Privacy Policy of GraceLink

This Privacy Policy outlines how GraceLink collects, uses, and protects your personal data when you use our application. We are committed to ensuring the privacy and security of your information.

**Owner and Data Controller**

Any inquiries regarding your Personal Data, its purposes, and the parties it is shared with can be directed to the Owner. The Owner and Data Controller of GraceLink is [Owner's Name] at [Owner's Address].

**Types of Data Collected**

GraceLink does not provide a list of Personal Data types collected. Complete details about the types of Personal Data collected are available in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or through specific explanation texts displayed before data collection. Users may provide Personal Data voluntarily or it may be collected automatically, especially Usage Data, when using the application. All data requested by GraceLink is mandatory unless explicitly stated otherwise, and failure to provide this data may result in the inability to access or use our services.

**Cookies and Tracking**

GraceLink may use cookies and other tracking tools to provide the service required by the user, in addition to other purposes described in this document and in the Cookie Policy.

**Mode and Place of Processing the Data**

GraceLink takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or destruction of data. Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT tools following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. Personal Data may be accessible to certain personnel involved with the operation of GraceLink or external parties appointed as Data Processors if necessary. Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and other locations where parties involved in processing are located.

**Retention Time**

Personal Data is processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose it was collected for, and may be retained longer due to legal obligations or User consent.

**Rights of Users**

Users have rights regarding their Personal Data processed by GraceLink, including the right to withdraw consent, object to processing, access, rectify, restrict processing, erase, receive data, and lodge a complaint. Users can exercise these rights by contacting the Owner.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

GraceLink reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy. Users will be notified of any changes by updating this page. It is recommended to review this page frequently for updates.

